# **Brittany Barba**

## **PROFILE**

Virginia based UX Designer with a target to create superb user experiences from use to visual appeal. I strive for beautiful solutions that captivates any audience.

<u>Tools</u>	Skills
Figma Adobe InVision Photoshop Sketch Flowmapp Office Suite Salesforce	HTML Java CSS Project Coordination Time Management Organization
Experience	

# Renovar- Onsite Program Supervisor

September 2020-Present

- Train and oversee a team of 5 to achieve all sales and cycle goals.
- Identify kinks and frustrations in the program and develop effective solutions to create an outstanding experience for clients.
- Create and update training manuals and current workflows for the program.
- Understand and assist in the needs and communications of homeowners, adjusters, public adjusters, contractors and repair firms about process updates, documentation, and other related needs and questions.
- Enter and maintain assignments information in Renovar database and carrier specific tools as required, such as Salesforce, CoreLogic, Xactimate, XactAnalysis and AlecNet.
- Execute the assignments procedures within the required time limits to ensure that all
  work, assignments, communication, forms, and questions, are properly and effectively
  handled within the parameters of our contractual obligations to our clients.
- Solve policyholders', adjusters', and repair firms' concerns through problem solving and teamwork from the Technical Analysis team, repair firms, and/or management.
- Be able to multitask daily by managing tasks, emails, and voicemails with timely responses to all.
- Be able to communicate reports with the insured and sell jobs to maintain goals.

#### Allianz- Senior Sales Associate

October 2018- August 2020

 Create and maintain a multi-tooled system that assists and tracks associate knowledge and metrics.

- Observe and record trends in team performance and provide feedback and actively support the team
- Research and create a policy that provides security and protection based on the client's needs.
- Meet or exceed all metrics while earning premium sales.
- Property and Casualty Licensed. (2019)

## Handyman Matters- Project Coordinator

March 2018-September 2018

- Manage the intake of all potential clients through multiple forms of communication.
- Develop, execute, and complete a wide variety of projects ranging from minor repairs to full renovations based on the clients needs.
- Manage the schedules of Craftsmen for all projects to ensure completion based on contract needs.
- Follow up with clients to create repeat business and high satisfaction rates.
- Create and execute training classes for craftsman and meetings based on necessit

# Education

### Career Foundry- UX Certificate

Intro to UX Design: Completed September 2021

• Fundamentals of research, personas, wireframing/prototyping, and testing.

Full UX Immersion: Completed June 2022

• Specialize in research, personas, wireframing/prototyping, testing, reiterations, finalizations, and presentation.

Frontend Development for Designers: Completion target August 2022

• Java, HTML, CSS

UI specialization for UX: Completion Target September 2022